Aleksandr Andrukhov

Sex: Male

Date of birth: 1997-02-12

Present Contact Address: Moscow, Russia

Permanent Contact Address: Rostov-On-Don, Russia

Nationality: Russian

Email: drammtv@gmail.com

Github: github.com/AlertRED

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/andrukhov-

aleksandr

WORK EXPERIENCE

KALABI - Backend developer

Dec 2022 - Apr 2023

Moscow, Russia

Development the API service in python. Flask, Flask-restplus, sqlalchemy, pytest, Redis, Postgresql, docker-compose technologies were used. Vue + typescript were also used for frontend. I was adding and expanding existing functionality, writing unit tests, and integrating with third-party services. Periodically worked with Docker-Compose and the frontend part of the project.

• Infotecs Internet Trust - Backend developer

Dec 2021 - Jul 2022

Moscow, Russia

Support for Legacy on Django and TypeScript and FastAPI a little bit, development of new functionality, also Pytest, Docker, Redis, RabbitMQ were used.

• FabLite - Backend developer

Nov 2020 - Oct 2021

Novosibirsk, Russia

Writing a REST API using FastAPI, developing sites using Flask, Django, writing documentation, working with Redis.

• 2-up - Backend developer

Apr 2019 - Aug 2019

Rostov-On-Don, Russia

PHP backend development - REST API writing, website parsing. Knowledge in Linux and SQL was applied.

EDUCATION

Harbin Institute of Technology, Computer Science - M.Sc. (in English)
Harbin, China
Sep 2019 - Jul 2022

GPA: 88.4/100.0

• **Don State Technical University,** Software Engineering - B.Sc.

Rostov-On-Don, Russia Sep 2015 - Jul 2019

GPA: 4.42/5.0, Final State Examination: 5.0/5.0, Graduation Thesis: 4.0/5.0

Relevant Coursework: Databases, Web-technologies, Object-oriented programming, Programming of mobile devices.

RESEARCH

 Recognition and measurement of vehicle speed in complex weather conditions

2022

A system based on deep learning to recognize vehicles on the roads in bad weather conditions. The system also calculates the transport speed using a special positioning algorithm.

Object recognition in a video stream

2019

The purpose of this paper is to simplify viewing of the traffic of objects in a video stream by identifying them using an object recognition application; presents algorithms for the implementation of the application. The source code for the modules is written in Python using the accompanying libraries.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Linux, Python3, Flask, FastAPI, Django, Vue3, SqlAlchemy, SOLID, SQL, Git, RabbitMQ, Redis

HONOR

2019 - Winner of Chinese Government Scholarship for Master Degree Program (3000 RMB/month stipend; exempt from registration fee, tuition fee, accommodation fee)

LANGUAGES

Russian - Mother language English - B1

2018

- Attack on information with the technologies of social engineering - International scientific and technical conference «System analysis, control and information processing» (SAC&IP) This article explores the technology of social engineering as an attack on information, as well as its main methods and highlights the ways in which they are used.
- 2017 Cluster analysis and basic algorithms of data clustering -International scientific and technical conference «System analysis, control and information processing» (SAC&IP), 2017 The analysis and sorting technology as clusterization are investigated, its main algorithms were analyzed. The main problems examined: how great is the effectiveness of the current clustering algorithms and theirs trends in the development.

SUMMARY

I am doing backend development in Python. The total experience in this programming language is more than 5 years. I try to stick to SOLID and KISS. In between jobs, I always do some pet project of my own and work freelance. I will be happy to learn something new (programming language, framework, technology, etc.). I am also interested in the field of data engineering.

I welcome relocation to another country or work remotely. The current English is at the B1 level and now I am actively working on improving it.